<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>History on Remembrances</title><link>https://madeindigio.github.io/remembrances-mcp/en/categories/history/</link><description>Recent content in History on Remembrances</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://madeindigio.github.io/remembrances-mcp/en/categories/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Origin of the Project</title><link>https://madeindigio.github.io/remembrances-mcp/en/blog/2025/the_origin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madeindigio.github.io/remembrances-mcp/en/blog/2025/the_origin/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project was born in mid-2025 after working extensively with AI assistants and having to provide context over and over again. The idea was to create a tool that would make information management and retrieval efficient and effective. There were different solutions at that time, but most were based on traditional text-only approaches:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Solutions based on markdown files or similar.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Solutions based on relational databases like SQLite.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>However, after working with RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) in some projects for semantic information search, I believed something better could be done. Around that time, the &lt;em>paper and open-source project&lt;/em> &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://github.com/mem0ai/mem0">Mem0&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> appeared, proposing an MCP server approach that stored information in structured knowledge graphs and other elements.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why is it called Remembrances?</title><link>https://madeindigio.github.io/remembrances-mcp/en/blog/2025/why_remembrances_name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madeindigio.github.io/remembrances-mcp/en/blog/2025/why_remembrances_name/</guid><description>&lt;p>The name &lt;strong>Remembrances&lt;/strong> carries a deep and special meaning that reflects the essence and purpose of the project. The word &amp;ldquo;remembrances&amp;rdquo; in English refers to &amp;ldquo;memories&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;recollections,&amp;rdquo; which perfectly encapsulates the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: to help preserve, organize, and access valuable information and knowledge.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The name was chosen to highlight the importance of remembering and safeguarding important data in a world where information can easily be lost. Remembrances acts as a guardian of these digital memories, ensuring that users can retrieve and use their information whenever they need it.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>